Guide to the David Hamburg papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Subseries III.1: Individuals
    - Lubic, Ruth Watson, 1983-1997 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - Lucas, Adetokunbo, 1977-1998 (Box 297, Folder 10-11)
    - Luck, Edward, 1989-1999 (Box 297, Folder 12)
    - Luers, William H., 1991-2000 (Box 297, Folder 13)
    - Lugar, Richard, 1986-2000 (Box 297, Folder 14)
    - Lu-Ly (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Lyman, Jing, 1981-1987 (Box 297, Folder 15)
    - Lyman, Richard, 1985-1998 (Box 297, Folder 16)
    - Maas, Jim, 1986-1994 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Mab - Manl, 1980-2000 (Box 285, Folder 19)
    - Maccoby, Eleanor, 1991-2001 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - MacFarlane, Lewis, 1976-2000 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - MacLane, Saunders, 1980-1992 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - MacVicar, Margaret, 1988-1991 (Box 299, Folder 7-8)
    - Madrid, Arturo, 1985-1988 (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Magnusson, David, 1994-1996 (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Maguire, Andrew, 1983-1989 (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Mahfouz, Mahmoud, 1978-1981 (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - Mahler, Halfda, 1982-1990 (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - Mahoney, Margaret, 1980-1998 (Box 299, Folder 14)
    - Makagiansar, Irwan, 1999- (Box 299, Folder 15)
    - Makagiansar, Makaminan, 1998-1999 (Box 299, Folder 16-17)
    - Malcom, Shirley, 1995-2000 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Malkin, Peter L., 1982-1993 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Mallison, David, 1992- (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Malone, David, 1999-2000 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Maloney, Carolyn, 1998- (Box 300)
    - Mandel, Arnold, 1981-1985 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Mandela, Nelson, 1991-1998 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Mandelbaum, Michael, 1988-1998 (Box 300, Folder 5-6)
    - Mankiewicz, Frank, 1982-1995 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Mann - Marq, 1980-2000 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1990-1994 (Folder 10)
    - Mar - Maz, 1977-1997 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Mark, James, 1972-2000 (Folder 11)
    - Marks, Paul A., 1979-1992 (Folder 12)
    - Maron, David, 1987- (Folder 13)
    - Marshall, Ray, 1996-1996 (Box 301, Folder 1-3)
    - Marshall, Ray, 1984-1999 (Folder 14-15)
    - Martin, Keith, 1998- (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Martin, Lynn, 1989-1994 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Sir Laurence, 1996- (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Martinez, Vilma, 1986-1987 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Marx, Martita, 1981-1983 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Massey, Walter E., 1983-1985 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Mathias, Charles McC., 1986-1998 (Box 301, Folder 10)
    - Mathysse, Steven, 1973-1981 (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Matlock, Jack F., 1983-1998 (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - Matsunaga, Spark, 1984-1986 (Box 301, Folder 13)
    - Matusack, Larraine, 1984-1996 (Box 301, Folder 14)
    - Matuszewski, Daniel C., 1989-1998 (Box 301, Folder 15)
    - Mawby, Russel G., 1980-1995 (Box 301, Folder 16)
    - Mayer, Jean, 1984-1992 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - McAdoo, Tina, 1981-1983 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - McB - McDe, 1981-1998 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - McCarty, Richard, 1999-2000 (Box 302, Folder 3-4)
    - McDermott, Walsh, 1978-1996 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - McDo, 1991-2000 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - McE - McZ, 1974-1999 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - McEwen, 1996- (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - McGinnis, J. Michael, 1980-1999 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - McGinnis, L.D., 1977-1981 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - McGowan, Alan, 1990-1998 (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - McGrew, W.C., 1971-1997 (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - McHugh, Matthew, 1985-1992 (Box 302, Folder 11)
    - McKeown, Thomas, 1975-1988 (Box 302, Folder 12)
    - McKinney, William, 1973-1987 (Box 302, Folder 13)
    - McNamara, Robert, 1977-1999 (Box 302, Folder 14)
    - McNeal, Edward (Ned), 1995-1997 (Box 302, Folder 15-16)
    - McNeill, Barbara, 1981-1997 (Box 302, Folder 17)
    - McNeill, William H., 1985-1996 (Box 302, Folder 18)
    - McNerney, Walter J., 1977-1982 (Box 302, Folder 19)
    - McPherson, Mary Patterson, 1994-1998 (Box 302, Folder 20)
    - Mea - Mez, 1983-2000 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Mechanic, David, 1976-1996 (Box 302, Folder 21)
    - Mehrabian, Robert, 1992-1995 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Meir, Golda, 1977- (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Melinkoff, Sherman, 1979-1983 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Menino, Thomas, 1996- (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Merhav, Hadar, 1981-1996 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Merrick, Nancy, 1972-2000 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Merton, Robert K., 1985-1992 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Meselson, Matthew, 1990-1998 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Mia-Miller, 1974-1996 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Midgett, Palmer S. Jr., 1979-1995 (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Jo Ann, 1980-1992 (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Kenneth, 1987-2000 (Box 303, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Margaret Carnegie, 1983-1990 (Box 303, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Neal E., 1980-1996 (Box 303, Folder 13)
    - Miller, William F., 1978-1989 (Box 303, Folder 14)
    - Milliken - Miz, 1981-2000 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Mills, Mark J., 1982-1984 (Box 303, Folder 15)
    - Milner, David, 1993-1993 (Box 303, Folder 17)
    - Milstein, Susan, 1988-1993 (Box 303, Folder 16)
    - Minow, Martha, 1982-2000 (Box 303, Folder 18-19)
    - Minow, Newton, 1994-2000 (Box 303, Folder 20-21)
    - Mitchell, Maria, 2000- (Box 303, Folder 22-23)
    - Moa - Mor, 1976-2000 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Moffett, Julia, ND- (Box 303, Folder 24)
    - Mohs, Richard C., 1990-1990 (Box 303, Folder 25)
    - Moody, Jim, 1991-1999 (Box 303, Folder 26)
    - Moore-Ede, Martin C., 1992-1993 (Box 303, Folder 27)
    - Moos, Rudolf H., 1978-1997 (Box 303, Folder 28)
    - Morrisett, Lloyd N., 1990-1997 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Mos - Moz, 1985-2000 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Mosher, Frederic A. "Fritz", 1984-1996 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Moshoeshoe II, King of Lesotho (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Mosteller, Frederick, 1982-1998 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Motulsky, Arno G., 1978-1999 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Moxley, John H III, 1980-1993 (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1989-1994 (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1982-1997 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Mr - Mz, 1981-1997 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Mroz, John, 1989-1995 (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - Msangi, A.S., 1972-1998 (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - Mueller, Carl M., 1983-1998 (Box 285, Folder 11)
    - Muller, Henry, 1994-2000 (Box 285, Folder 12-14)
    - Murphy, John, 1990-1993 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - Murray, Robert Fulton, 1990-1993 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - Murray, Robert J., 1988-1993 (Box 285, Folder 17)
    - Myrdal, Gunnar, 1982-1984 (Box 285, Folder 18)
    - Na - Ne, 1982-2000 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - Naggan, Lechaim, M.D., 1981-1983 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Nagy, Laszlo, 1989-1998 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Nestle, Marion, 1987-1988 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Newell, David, 1983- (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Newman, Alan H., 1986-2000 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Newsom, Barbara, 1981-1995 (Box 305, Folder 11-14)
    - Ni - Nz, 1973-2001 (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Nichols, Rodney W., 1983-1999 (Box 306, Folder 1-5)
    - Nielsen, Waldemar, 1984-2000 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Nightingale, Elena O., 1981-2001 (Box 306, Folder 7-22)
    - Noble, Ernest, 1973-1999 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Nordheimer, Jon, 1982- (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Nossal, G.J.V., 1982- (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Novello, Antonia, 1990-1992 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Nunn, Michelle, 1989-1999 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Nunn, Sam, 1987-2002 (Box 307, Folder 6-32)
    - Nunn, Sam, 1985-1997 (Box 308, Folder 1-2)
    - Nye, Joseph, 1984-2000 (Box 308, Folder 3-5)
    - Oa - Om, 1980-2000 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Obasanjo, Olusegun, 1986-1999 (Box 308, Folder 8-14)
    - Obasanjo, Olusegun, 1996-1999 (Box 309, Folder 1-6)
    - Ochberg, Frank, 1971-1990 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - O'Connell, Brian, 1983-1989 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Odhiambo, Thomas, 1992-1997 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Ogata, Sadako, 1997-2001 (Box 309, Folder 10-12)
    - Ogletree, Charles J., 1991-1994 (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - O'Keefe, Michael, 1986-1995 (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Okun, Herbert, 1988-1999 (Box 309, Folder 15-18)
    - Olds, David L., 1991-1993 (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Omenn, Gilbert S., 1978-1997 (Box 309, Folder 20)
    - On - Oz, 1981-2000 (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Osmundsen, Lita, 1983-1998 (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Osnos, Peter, 1992-2000 (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Ossipyan, (Academician) Yuri A., 1991- (Box 309, Folder 23)
    - Otunnu, Olara A., 1991-1999 (Box 309, Folder 24-25)
    - Owada, Hisashi, 1996-2000 (Box 309, Folder 26)
    - Owen, David (Right Honorable), 1994-1999 (Box 309, Folder 27)
    - Pac - Pay, 1977-1998 (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Packard, David & Lucille, 1984-1996 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Packer, Craig, 1973-1994 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Panofsky, Wolfgang, 1988-1998 (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Papamarkou, Alexander, 1985-1997 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Pardes, Herbert, 1980-1999 (Box 310, Folder 7-8)
    - Parron, Delores, 1980-2000 (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Patterson, Neil (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Pauley, Jane, 1982-2000 (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Payton, Robert L., 1983-1993 (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Pe, 1976-2000 (Box 313, Folder 4-5)
    - Pearce, Terry & Tom Green, 1984-1985 (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Pearlman, Clifford, 1995- (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Peck, Connie, 1994-2000 (Box 310, Folder 15-21)
    - Pelosi, Nancy, 1984-2000 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1997- (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Perez, Julene, 1995- (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Perlman, David, 1985-1992 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Perpich, Joseph G,. M.D., 1976-1997 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Perry, Bruce, 1995- (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Perry, William J., 1983-2000 (Box 311, Folder 7-11)
    - Petersdorf, Robert G., 1979-1991 (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Petersen, Anne, 1980-1998 (Box 311, Folder 13-16)
    - Petersen, Mary Louise, 1982-1996 (Box 311, Folder 17)
    - Peterson, Dale, 1997- (Box 311, Folder 18)
    - Peterson, Peter G., 1992-1993 (Box 311, Folder 19)
    - Petros-Barvazian, Angela, 1982-1995 (Box 311, Folder 20)
    - Pettit, Joesph M., 1983- (Box 311, Folder 21)
    - Pf-Pi (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Pf-Pi (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Pickering, Thomas, 1989-1998 (Box 311, Folder 22)
    - Pifer, Alan, 1985-1986 (Box 311, Folder 23)
    - Pifer, Alan, 1980-1996 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Pl-Po (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Pl-Pz (Box 314, Folder 3-4)
    - Porter, Roger, 1989-1992 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Potkin, Steven, 1979-2000 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Prager, Denis J., 1983-1993 (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Press, Frank, 1979-1995 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Price, Richard H., 1987-1996 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Prince Aga Khan, 1983-1990 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Pritzker, Jay and Cindy, 1990-1999 (Box 312, Folder 7-11)
    - Prothrow-Stith, Deborah, 1991-1995 (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Prywes, Moshe, M.D., 1977-1995 (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Puck, Theodore T., 1984-1994 (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Pusey, Anne, 1971-1996 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Putnam, Robert, 1989-1993 (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Q (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Quinn, Jane, 1991-1999 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Rabinowitch, Alexander, 1989-1991 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Rabinowitch, Victor, 1988-2000 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Racusen, Seth, 1989- (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Ramalingaswami, Vulmiri, 1980-1999 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Ramo, Simon, 1984-1993 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Ramphal, Sir Shridath, 1982-1984 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Ramphele, Mamphela, 1987-1999 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Randolph, Linda A., 1990-1993 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Rangel, Charles, 1984-1994 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Ra-Rez (Box 321, Folder 4-6)
    - Ra-Rez (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Raspberry, William, 1992-1994 (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Ratchford, J. Thomas, 1985-1995 (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Ratliff, Floyd, 1983- (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - Raven, Peter, 1993-1996 (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - Redford, Robert, 1985- (Box 315, Folder 14)
    - Redlich, Fritz, 1974-1998 (Box 315, Folder 15)
    - Reich, Walter, 1986-1994 (Box 315, Folder 16)
    - Reiner, Rob, 1997-2000 (Box 315, Folder 17-18)
    - Relman, Arnold, 1982-1992 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Renier, Chriss, 1986-1988 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Reno, Janet, 1993-2001 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Rhoades, Lawrence, 1987- (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Rh-Ri (Box 322, Folder 2-5)
    - Rice, Dorothy, 1980-1990 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Rich, Richard, 1983- (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Richardson, Elliot, 1981-2000 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Richardson, Yolanda, 1989-1995 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Richmond, Julius, 1980-2000 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Rickert, Jonathan, 2002- (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - Riley, Matilda, 1979-1997 (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Riley, Richard, 1992-2001 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Rimel, Rebecca W., 1985-1986 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Riss, David, 1971-1981 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Rivera, Jose, 1996-1997 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Rivera, Tomas, 1983-1984 (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Antony, 1982-1986 (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Robbins, Frederick C, 1980-1999 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Robinson, David Z., 1984-1994 (Box 317, Folder 7-8)
    - Rob-Ros (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Rob-Ros (Box 323, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, David Jr, 1983-1997 (Box 317, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David Sr., 1982-2000 (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV, 1991-1996 (Box 317, Folder 11)
    - Rockoff, Maxine L., 1990-1994 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Rodin, Judith, 1993-1999 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Rogers, David E., 1978-1994 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Rogers, Paul G., 1978-1996 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Romer, Roy, 1991-1997 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Roosa, Robert V., 1983-1984 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Rose, Charlie, 1994-1999 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - Rose, Robert, 1982-1998 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - Rosecrace, Richard, 1997-1999 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - Rosenblith, Judy F., 1989-1992 (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - Rosenblith, Walter A., 1981-2000 (Box 318, Folder 11)
    - Rosenfield, Allan, 1993-1993 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Rosenfield, Patricia L., 1983-1996 (Box 319, Folder 2-3)
    - Rosenheim, Margaret "Peggy", 1978-1996 (Box 319, Folder 4-5)
    - Rosenstreich, Judy P., 1985- (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Rosenthal, A.M., 1993-1999 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Rosenthal, Jack, 1987-1996 (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Rosenzweig, Robert M., 1977-1995 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Rosenzweig, Saul, 1980-1984 (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Rosewater, Ann, 1984-1994 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Ros-Rz (Box 323, Folder 3-5)
    - Ros-Rz (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Rowe, John W. "Jack", 1980-2000 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Rubin, Ephraim, 1989-1991 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Rubin, Judy, 1992-1998 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Rubin, Robert E., 1990-1993 (Box 320, Folder 5-6)
    - Rubin, Robert T., 1976-1981 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Rudenstine, Neil L., 1991-2000 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Russell, Avery, 1984-1994 (Box 321, Folder 1-2)
    - Rutherford, F. James, 1990-1997 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Saa-Shw (Box 333, Folder 4-7)
    - Sabiston, David Jr, 1977-1996 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Sabshin, Mel, 1996- (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Saft, Virginia, 1985-1996 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Sagdeev, Roald, 1985-1994 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Sai, Fred, 1984-1986 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Sakharov, Andrei, 1988- (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Salk, Jonas, 1981-1988 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Samuel, Rinna, 1977-1999 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Sanders, Charles A., 1981-1999 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Sandwick, Mary Lou, 2000-2001 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1977-1991 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Sarbanes, Paul S., 1985-1992 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Sartorius, Norman, 1980-1998 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Saudek, Chris, 1980- (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Saunders, Stewart, 1985-1998 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Sawhill, Isabel, 1988-1997 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Sawyer, John Edward, 1979-1993 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Schaengold, Phillip, 1997- (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - Schearer, Bruce, 1990-1991 (Box 325, Folder 12)
    - Scheffler, Richard M., 1975-1985 (Box 325, Folder 13)
    - Schelling, Thomas, 1983-1999 (Box 325, Folder 14)
    - Schiffer, Daniella, 1984- (Box 325, Folder 15)
    - Schine, Joan G, 1987-1994 (Box 325, Folder 16)
    - Schoettle, Enid, 1989-1996 (Box 325, Folder 17)
    - Schorr, Daniel, 1983-1987 (Box 325, Folder 18)
    - Schorr, Lisbeth, 1975-2000 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Sco-Shu (Box 334, Folder 1-4)
    - Scott, Andrew, 1983-1986 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Ann Firor, 1980-1986 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Robert A., 1991-1999 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Seaborg, Glenn T., 1983-1994 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Sebeok, Thomas E., 1979-1984 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Seeman, Philip, 1979- (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - Selby, Cecily Cannan, 1984- (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - Selye, Hans, 1974-1979 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - Sewell, John, 1985-1998 (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - Shakhashiri, Bassam Z., 1986-1994 (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - Shalala, Donna, 1984-2001 (Box 326, Folder 12-13)
    - Shapiro, Harold, 1985-1996 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Sharfstein, Steven S., 1978-1981 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Shattuck, John, 1993-1997 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Sheffield, Jill, 1983-1999 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Sheldon, Alan, 1980-1981 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Shenker, Joseph, 1992-1994 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Sheppard, Audrey, 1987- (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Sheps, Cecil G., 1980-1991 (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Shesser, Robert, 1997- (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - Shine, Kenneth, 1992-2000 (Box 327, Folder 11)
    - Shore, Miles, 1981-1982 (Box 327, Folder 12)
    - Shriver, Sargent, 1977-1993 (Box 327, Folder 13)
    - Shulman, Marshall, 1984-1998 (Box 327, Folder 14)
    - Shultz, George, 1984-1996 (Box 327, Folder 15)
    - Sia-Smu (Box 334, Folder 5-6)
    - Sia-Smu (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Sidamon-Eristoff, Anne, 1994-2000 (Box 327, Folder 16)
    - Sifton, Elisabeth, 2000- (Box 327, Folder 17)
    - Simmons, Adele, 1989-1998 (Box 327, Folder 18)
    - Simmons, Adele, 1988-1989 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Simon, Harold J., 1977-1998 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Simon, Paul, 1984-1998 (Box 328, Folder 3-4)
    - Simpson, Alan, 1986-2000 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Singer, Maxine, 1988-2000 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Singer, Milton, 1989-1992 (Box 328, Folder 7)
    - Slater, Joseph, 1986- (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Slavin, Robert, 1991-1998 (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Smelser, Neil J, 1994-1998 (Box 328, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Edgar, 1978-1981 (Box 328, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Gerard (Box 328, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Hedrick, 1992-1998 (Box 328, Folder 13)
    - Smith, John F. Sandy, 1991-1997 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Kenneth B., 1986-2000 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Larry, 1984-2000 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Marshall S., 1993-2000 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Philip, 1982-1994 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Steve, 1987-1995 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Smuts, Barbara, 1971-1998 (Box 329, Folder 7-9)
    - Snu-Sta (Box 335, Folder 2-4)
    - Snyder, Solomon, 1979-1981 (Box 329, Folder 10)
    - Snyder, Thomas E., 1977- (Box 329, Folder 11)
    - Soberon, Guillermo, 1983-1998 (Box 329, Folder 12)
    - Solarz, Stephen, 1985-1992 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Solnit, Albert, 1978-2000 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Solomon, Ari, 1984- (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Solomon, Frederic, 1979-1998 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Solomon, George, 1977-1994 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Solomon, Micah, 1981-1983 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Solomon, Richard, 1984-1998 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Somers, Anne, 1977-1987 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Sonneborn, T.M., 1976-1981 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - Soros, George, 1992-1998 (Box 330, Folder 10)
    - Spaeth, C. Grant, 1983-1990 (Box 330, Folder 11)
    - Sparks, Robert, 1978-1994 (Box 330, Folder 12)
    - Speedie, David, 1994-2000 (Box 330, Folder 13-14)
    - Spellman, Mitchell, 1977-1986 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Speth, James Gustave, 1990-2000 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Stamler, Jeremiah, 1979-1980 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Stark, Nathan J., 1977-1993 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Ste (Box 335, Folder 5-6)
    - Ste (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Steele, Thomas E., 1975-1985 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Steinbruner, John, 1984-1999 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Steinbruner, Maureen S., 1984-1995 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Stepp, Laura Sessions, 1995-1999 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Sterling, Wallace, 1977-1981 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Stern, Alfred, 1986-2000 (Box 331, Folder 10)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1987-1999 (Box 331, Folder 11)
    - Stewart, Vivian, 1984-1999 (Box 331, Folder 12-13)
    - Stewart-Teitelbaum, Abigail, 2000-2001 (Box 331, Folder 14)
    - Stewart-Teitelbaum, Emma, 1999- (Box 331, Folder 15)
    - Sti-Sul (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Sti-Sz (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Stone, James, 1982-1985 (Box 331, Folder 14)
    - Strauss, Robert, 1991- (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Stremlau, John, 1984-2000 (Box 332, Folder 2-4)
    - Strong, Maurice, 1983-2000 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Strum, Shirley, 1982-1998 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Stunkard, Albert J., 1982-2000 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Sugarman, Jule, 1988- (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Sullivan, Louis, 1977-1998 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur O, 1988-2000 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Sum-Sz (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Sutherland, John, 1977- (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Taber, George, 1980-1984 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Takanishi, Ruby, 1981-1999 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Talbott, Strobe, 1993-2001 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Tarlov, Alvin R., 1979-1984 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Tarnoff, Peter, 1991-1999 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Ta-Ti (Box 267, Folder 1-2)
    - Taubman, Philip, 1996-1998 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Carl, 1977-1980 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Humphrey, 1983-1995 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Taylor, John C III, 1983-2000 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Tecce, Joseph J., 1980-1982 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Teitelbaum, Michael, 1983-1999 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Teltsch, Kathleen, 1982-1995 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Tempelsman, Maurice, 1999- (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Theodore, Mary, 1999- (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Thier, Samuel O., 1985-1998 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, Franklin, 1983-1986 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Lewis, 1984-1984 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Vinod, 1996- (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Thornburgh, Dick, 1988-1989 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Tienda, Marta, 1998-1999 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Tiger, Lionel, 1977-1990 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Tilson, David, 1978-1981 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Tinklenberg, Jared, 1975-1976 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Tisch, Wilma S "Billie", 1993-1996 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Tishkov, Valerie, 1992-1998 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Ti-Tz (Box 267, Folder 3-4)
    - Topping, Seymour, 1982-1984 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Tosteson, Daniel C., 1978-1997 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Towers, Bernard, 1977- (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Troyer, Thomas, 1985-1999 (Box 338, Folder 13-14)
    - Troyer, Thomas, 1977-1985 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Trudeau, Michelle, 1982-1999 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Tsukada, Irene, 1985-1991 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Tucker, Marc, 1984-1986 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Tuminez, Astrid, 1992-2001 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Turmer, Ted, 2000- (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Turner, Stansfield, 1986-1999 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Tutu, Desmond, 1984-2000 (Box 339, Folder 8-9)
    - U (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Unger, Walter J., 1979-1992 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Upton, Arthur, 1977-1997 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Ury, William L., 1984-1999 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Usdin, Earl, 1977-1983 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - V (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Vagelos, P. Roy, 1979-1996 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - van der Vink, Gregory E., 1986-1984 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Vance, Cyrus, 1976-1999 (Box 340, Folder 7-8)
    - VanderStoep, Annie, 1972-1978 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Vartanyan, Marat Ye, 1979-1985 (Box 340, Folder 11)